FontName=
FontSize=

0001=(%c:)をディスク%dで作成
0002=システム
0003=コピー
0004=%cのコピー
0005=OSをディスク%dに移動
0006=(%c:)をディスク%dにコピー
0007=ディスク%dをディスク%dにコピー
0008=ディスク(%c:)をディスク%dから削除
0009=(%c:)を%sでフォーマット
0010=(%c:)のボリュームラベルを%sに設定
0011=ドライブ文字(%c:)を(%c:)に変更
0012=パーティション%s(%c:)を非表示
0013=パーティション%s(%c:)を再表示
0014=(%c:)をディスク%dでアクティブパーティションに設定
0015=パーティション%c:を%dセクタにアライメント
0016=パーティション(%c:)のサイズをディスク%dで調整
0017=(%c:)パーティションをディスク%dで移動
0018=(%c:)のサイズをディスク%dで移動し調整
0019=(%c:)をディスク%dでNTFSへ変換
0020=(%c:)を基本パーティションへ変換
0021=(%c:)を論理パーティションへ変換
0022=ディスク%dのパーティション全体削除
0023=ディスク%dの未割り当て領域を消去
0024=ディスク%dを消去
0025=パーティション(%c:)を消去
0026=パーティション(%c:)の種類を0x%02Xに変更
0027=パーティション(%c:)のシリアル番号を変更
0028=ディスク%dのMBRをリビルド
0029=ディスク%dを初期化
0030=ディスク%dをMBRへ変換
0031=ディスク%dをGPTへ変換

0032=現在の実行ステータス:%s/%s
0033=現在の実行回数:%d  実行ステータス:%s/%s
0034=移動データ:%s/%s
0035=処理が終わりました。しばらくお待ちください…
0036=システムと同期化しています。しばらくお待ちください…

0037=ディスク:\t\t\t
0038=ドライブ文字:\t\t
0039=ファイルシステム:\t\t
0040=ボリュームラベル:\t\t

0041=サイズ:\t\t\t
0042=パーティションを作成
0043=ソースディスク:\t\t
0044=ターゲットディスク:\t\t
0045=OSをSSD/HDDに移動
0046=パーティションをコピー
0047=クラスターのサイズ:\t\t
0048=パーティションをフォーマット
0049=パーティションを削除
0050=新しいボリュームラベル:\t
0051=ボリュームラベルを変更
0052=ドライブ文字を変更
0053=パーティションを非表示
0054=パーティションを表示
0055=アクティブに設定
0056=パーティションのアライメント:\t
0057=パーティションのアライメント
0058=先頭セクタ:\t\t
0059=パーティションのサイズを調整
0060=パーティションを移動
0061=パーティションを調整し移動
0062=パーティションの種類:\t
0063=NTFSパーティションへ変換
0064=基本パーティションへ変換
0065=論理パーティションへ変換
0066=データの消去:\t\t
0067=パーティション全体削除
0068=消去回数:\t\t
0069=データの消去
0070=ディスクの消去
0071=パーティションの消去
0072=
0073=
0074=ディスクのコピー:\t\t
0075=コピー方法:\t\t
0076=ディスクのコピー
0077=基本 -> 論理
0078=論理 -> 基本
0079=変換元:\t\t\t
0080=パーティションの原サイズ:\t
0081=パーティションの新しいサイズ:\t
0082=パーティションを縮小して作成
0083=パーティションの分割
0084=パーティションの結合
0085=パーティションの種類の変更
0086=旧シリアル番号:\t\t
0087=新シリアル番号:\t\t
0088=シリアル番号の変更
0089=MBRのリビルド
0090=スタイル:\t\t\t
0091=ディスクを初期化
0092=MBRをGPTへ変換
0093=GPTをMBRへ変換
0094=はい
0095=いいえ

0096=空き領域を使用
0097=
0098=あるディスクの空き領域を他のパーティションに割り当てます。
0099=(%c:)から:
0100=現在の(%c:)のサイズは%sで、ディスク(%c:)のサイズは%sです。
0101=Please first click Apply on the toolbar to commit the previous pending operation.

0102=処理の実行を待っています
0103=AOMEI Partition Assistantは準備ができました。下記の処理を確認してください。
0104=「実行」ボタンをクリックして、アプリケーションの処理を正式に実行してください。
0105=現在の処理%d、すべての処理%d\n
0106=  (PCを再起動する必要があります)
0107=<b>试用版</b>続行できません。
0108=今からこれらの処理を実行してよろしいでしょうか。
0109=これらの処理を実行するために、PCを再起動する必要があります。よろしいでしょうか。再起動後システムに入る前にアプリケーションがPreOSモードで実行して来これらのパーティション処理を実現します。
0110=<system>\ampa.exeまたは<system>\system32\ampa.sysファイルが見つかりません。アプリケーションを再インストールすることをすすめます。
0111=PreOSの配置ファイルの更新に失败しました。
0112=レジストリの編集に失败しました。アンチウィルスソフトまたはファイアウォールがこの処理を期限する可能性がありますので、中止してください。
0113=PCの再起動に失败しました。手作業でPCを再起動してください。
0114=<b>処理可能時間:</b> これらの処理を完了するまで<b>%s</b>以上かかるかもしれません。
0115=購入
0116=试用版ですが、完全版を購入する必要があります。\n\nこの製品が好きな方は、このリンク<u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/purchase.html?pa">http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/</a></font></u>クリックしてご購入ください。\n\n\n<b>试用版の制限:</b> 100MBを超えたパーティション処理は実行不可。<br>そしてパーティションで100MBを超えたサイズを拡大・縮小<br>ができません。

0117=sales@aomeitech.com
0118=试用版ですが、完全版を購入する必要があります。\n\nこの製品が好きな方は、「購入」ボタンをクリックしてください。あるいは<font color="#0000f0"><a href="mailto:%s">%s</a></font>までご連絡ください。\n\n\n<b>试用版の制限:</b> 100MBを超えたパーティション処理は実行不可。<br>そしてパーティションで100MBを超えたサイズを拡大・縮小<br>ができません。
0119=購入(&B)
0120=キャンセル(&C)


0121=ヘルプ(&H)
0122=確認(&O)
0123=実行(&P)


0124=パーティションのドライブ文字を変更
0125=
0126=新しいドライブ文字(&L):
0127=パーティションのドライブ文字を変更。
0128=USBメモリーデバイス上で、Windowsは初めての基本パーティションしか識別できません。基本パーティションがない場合、初めての論理パーティションしか識別できません。しかし選択されたパーティションは初めてではないので、ドライブ文字の設定ができません。
0129=無し

0130=パーティションの現在の種類ID:
0131=パーティションの新しい種類ID:
0132=選択されたパーティションの種類IDを変更。

0133=新シリアル番号(16进制):
0134=パーティションのシリアル番号を変更。

0135=パーティションをチェック
0136=chkdsk.exeを使って、パーティションのエラーをチェック(&E)
0137=パーティションの不良セクタをチェック(&W)
0138=エラーをチェックするパーティションを選択してください。
0139=オプション


0140=チェック更新
0141=チェック中…
0142=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/upgrade.ini
0143=サーバーへの接続は失敗しました。インターネットに正常に接続できることを確認してください。
0144=情報
0145=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/
0146=最新バージョン(%d.%d)が検出されています。もっと情報を知りたいですか。\n\n%s
0147=すでに最新バージョンです。

0148=パーティション全体削除(&D)
0149=パーティション全体削除とディスクデータ全体消去(&E)
0150=このディスクではシステムパーティションを含めます。システムパーティションが削除されると、PCが起動できませんので、よろしいでしょうか。
0151=ディスクデータ全体消去

0152=パーティションはエラーがあります。chkdsk.exe /fコマンドを使って修復してから、変換を行ってください。
0153=選択されたパーティションのファイルシステムを変換。
0154=NTFSへ変換するには、PCを再起動する必要がありますので、よろしいでしょうか。
0155=
0156=
0157=このパーティションで実行中のアプリケーションがありますので、変換処理が続けません。正常に続けるために、そられのアプリケーションを閉じてください。よろしいでしょうか。
0158=GPT/MBRを変換
0159=MBRとGPTディスク間の変換。
0160=アプリケーションはWindowsのページファイル(pagefile.sys)が%c:パーティションにあることを検出しました。それを一時削除してからこの処理を再試行してください。
0161=アプリケーションはダイナミックディスクを%sディスクへの変換がサポートされていません。AOMEI Dynamic Disk Converter(ダイナミックディスク変換器)を使ってこのディスクを基本ディスクへ変換してから再試行することをすすめます。
0162=システムディスク変換後は再起動できませんので、システムディスクはGPTとMBRディスク間の変換がサポートされていません。
0163=このディスクは2TBを超えて、パーティションを保有していますので、MBRへ変換できません。このディスクのパーティション全体を削除してから、変換の実行ができます。

0164=The partition layout of current disk cannot meet the requirement of conversion, please refer to FAQ for more help.
0165=このGPTディスクをMBRディスクへ変換してよろしいでしょうか。
0166=現在のOS(WinXPまたはWin2000)はGPTディスクがサポートされていませんので、このディスクをGPTへ変換できません。GPTディスクが使用できるには、システムをWin7またはServer2008にアップデートすることをすすめます。
0167=このMBRディスクをGPTディスクへ変換してよろしいでしょうか。
0168=このディスクをGPTへ変換するためのディスク領域が足りません。详细情報はFAQをご参照ください。

0169=基本・論理への変換
0170=基本パーティションと論理パーティション間の変換。
0171=選択されたパーティション"%s(%c:)"は基本パーティションから論理パーティションに変換します。
0172=このパーティションの空き領域が256MB以下で、論理パーティションへ変換できません。パーティションに使用しないファイルを削除して、256MB以上の領域を解放してから変換を実行することをすすめます。
0173=選択されたパーティション"%s(%c:)"は論理パーティションから基本パーティションに変換します。

0174=パーティションのボリュームラベル(&L):
0175=ドライブ文字(&D):
0176=種類設定(&C):
0177=ファイルシステム(&F):
0178=サイズと位置
0179=パーティションする前の未割り当て領域(&U):
0180=パーティションのサイズ(&S):
0181=パーティションする後の未割り当て領域(&F):
0182=SSDパーティションのアライメント(&A):
0183=詳細(&A)
0184=新しいパーティションのサイズと位置に関する情報を設定してください。
0185=入力されたボリュームラベルは最大長を超えました。
0186=移動できるデバイスで、Windowsは初めての基本パーティションしか識別できません。基本パーティションがない場合、初めての論理パーティションしか識別できません。新規作成のパーティションはドライブ文字がありませんが、続けてよろしいでしょうか。
0187=論理パーティション
0188=基本パーティション
0189=選択された未割り当て領域のサイズが足りないので、パーティションを作成できません。
0190=選択されたこの未割り当て領域でパーティションを作成できません。
0191=フォーマットしていない
0192=デフォルト

0193=SSDパーティションアライメント最適化(&P)
0194=新しいパーティションのサイズ:
0195=新規作成のパーティションのサイズを指定します。
0196=アプリケーションは%s領域を%c:ディスクから割り当て、新パーティションを作成します。%c:ディスクは%sに減縮されます。

0197=パーティションの削除(&D)
0198=選択されたパーティションを削除またはこのパーティションのすべてのデータを消去します。
0199=パーティションを削除してデータを消去(&E)

0200=パーティションを閲覧
0201=このパーティションのルート配下のすべてのファイルを確認します。
0202=ファイルをローディングしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0203=キャンセルしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0204=ファイルをこのパーティションで見つかれませんでした。

0205=すみませんが、現在の処理がキャンセルされました。\r\n情報コード: %d\r\n
0206=説明: 
0207=\r\nもっと情報: 
0208=パーティションテーブルが他のアプリケーションに使っていますので、編集に失败しました。すべての他のアプリケーションを閉じて再試行してください。
0209=ドライブ文字を変更する時にGUIDの割り当てが失败しました。PCを再起動してから再試行してください。
0210=このディスクのパーティションテーブルが重なっています。
0211=この処理はユーザーよりキャンセルされました。
0212=Windows制御コードを使ってこのパーティションの拡大に失败しました。
0213=碎片ファイルが多すぎです。パーティションをデフラグして置いてください。あるいはパーティションの空き領域が足りません。

0214=クラスターのサイズ:
0215=選択されたパーティションをフォーマット
0216=パーティションをフォーマットする場合、このパーティションのデータ全体が消去されます。
0217=デフォルト(%s)

0218=
0219=
0220=

0221=選択された非表示のパーティションを再表示。
0222=選択されたパーティションを非表示。
0223=このパーティションを再表示すると、このパーティションにドライブ文字を自動的に割り当ててよろしいでしょうか。
0224=このパーティションを非表示すると、このパーティションのドライブ文字が変更されますので、よろしいでしょうか。

0225=このディスクをMBRまたはGPTディスクに初期化します。
0226=ディスクに初期化:

0227=
0228=
0229=
0230=

0231=ロックされたボリューム
0232=ディスク%dをロックしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0233=パーティション(%c:)をロックしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0234=ボリュームが3分間以上ロックされました。「キャンセル」ボタンをクリックして終了してください。PCを再起動してから再試行してください。

0235=ディスクの選択:
0236=上記に選択されたパーティションをこのターゲットパーティションへ結合:
0237=二つ隣り合ったパーティションを一つに結合します。あるいは未割り当て領域を一つのパーティションに結合します。
0238=あるデータパーティションをシステムパーティションに結合する場合、システムパーティションのファイルシステムがNTFSであることが必要です。現在のシステムパーティションがFAT32で、システムパーティションをNTFSへ変換してからこの結合処理が正常に実行できます。
0239=ディスク%d
0240=未割り当て
0241=現在このアプリケーションはNTFSとFAT32パーティションの結合しかサポートされていません。
0242=ターゲットパーティションを選択してください。
0243=結合したいパーティションを二つ選択してください。
0244=Please first click Apply on the toolbar to commit the previous pending operations, and retry.
0245=ディスク%d (GPT)
0246=ディスク%d (移動できる)
0247=アプリケーションはあるNTFSパーティションをFAT32パーティションに結合できません。FAT32をNTFSへ変換してから結合できます。
0248=ディスク(%c:)のデータ全体が%c:\copied-driveに結合されます。
0249=ディスク(%c:)のデータ全体が%c:\%c-driveに結合されます。 
0250=ブートパーティションとシステムパーティションが一つに結合できません。
0251=システムパーティションまたはブートパーティションは前のパーティションと結合できません。
0252=システムパーティションとブートパーティションはデータパーティションに結合できません。

0253=スクロールバーをドラッグしてパーティションの位置を移動してください。
0254=領域が足りません。未割り当て領域のサイズ%s以上必要があります。(%c:)パーティションを縮小して来解放出更多領域以实现この移動パーティション処理、または購入一份<font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/get-full.html"><b>AOMEI Partition Assistant完全版</b></a></font>来实现更灵活のパーティション処理。

0255=このパーティションを移動したい(&I)。
0256=パーティションアライメントを許可して、SSDまたはHDDディスクを最適化します(&A)。
0257=请拖动下記のパーティション块为パーティション指定一个新しいサイズまたは位置。
0258=選択されたパーティションを希望位置に移動します。
0259=在調整你のパーティションサイズ之前我们建议你バックアップ你の重要データ。

0260=パーティションアライメントの設定:
0261=SSDまたはHDDディスクを最適化するために、パーティションアライメントをします。
0262=現在パーティションは選択されたセクタに従ってアライメントしていますので、もう一回アライメントする必要がありません。
0263=%d セクタ

0264=処理進捗
0265=総進捗
0266=現在の進捗
0267=すべての処理を完了した後自動的にパワーダウンされます(&S)。
0268=この処理をキャンセルしますか。「確認」ボタンをクリックした後、アプリケーションは本処理を実行した後に自動的にキャンセルされます。データ不整合を避けるために、アプリケーションのプロセスを強制終了しないでください。
0269=Congratulation! All operations have been completed successfully.<br><br>You can review the freeware and share your experience and happiness with others on the website <u><font color="#0000ff"><a href="http://download.cnet.com/AOMEI-Partition-Assistant-Standard-Edition/3000-2248_4-75118871.html#submitOrUpdateArea">CNET.com</a></font></u>, thanks!

0270=プロパティ
0271=%s (ディスク%d)
0272=   通常   
0273=   パーティション情報   
0274=   ファイルシステム情報   

0275=再試行(おすすめの処理)(&R)
0276=PCを再起動(&R)
0277=キャンセル処理(&C)
0278=処理方法を選択してください：\n\n1、「再試行」ボタンをクリックしてこれらのパーティションで実行されている他のアプリケーションを閉じてください。(おすすめの方法)\n2、クリック「再起動」ボタン让AOMEI Partition Assistant在再起動モード中完了これらのパーティション処理。\n3、キャンセル本次処理、你可以PCを再起動并再試行。
0279=パーティション(%s)が使用されていますので、これらの処理が完了できません。

0280=現在のOSのMBR種類の設定:
0281=MBRを修復にリビルドまたはMBRにブートコードを追加。

0282=ディスクをローディング
0283=ディスクデバイスをローディングしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0284=すみませんが、ディスクを見つかりませんでした。システムのディスクが他のアプリケーションによってロックされている可能性があるため、AOMEI Partition Assistantがこれらのディスクにアクセスできません。PCを再起動して再試行してください。

0285=選択されたパーティションをアクティブパーティションに設定します。
0286=このパーティションをアクティブパーティションに設定して、このディスクの他の基本パーティションを非アクティブステータスになってよろしいでしょうか。

0287=パーティションボリュームラベル(&P):
0288=選択されたパーティションにボリュームラベルを設定します。

0289=EXT4
0290=%c、*、%cを%cに結合
0291=%c、%cを%cに結合
0292=未割り当て領域を%cに結合
0293=(%c:)を縮小して(%c:)を作成
0294=(%c:)を分割して(%c:)を作成
0295=
0296=
0297=
0298=
0299=
0300=

0301=完全版を購入(&G)
0302=簡略版はこの機能がサポートされていません。<font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/get-full.html">http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/</a></font>をアクセスして完全版を購入できます。
0303=何かご質問がありましたら、ご遠慮なくメールでご連絡ください: <font color="#0000f0"><a href="mailto:support@aomeitech.com">support@aomeitech.com</a></font>または<font color="#0000f0"><a href="mailto:sales@aomeitech.com">sales@aomeitech.com</a></font>
0304=処理は続けませんので、本製品の完全版をご購入ください。
0305=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/get-full.html

0306=元のパーティションのサイズ:

0307=データの書き換え回数(&P):
0308=選択された未割り当て領域のデータ全体を消去します。
0309=1から100までの整数を入力してください。

0310=ディスク消去回数の指定(&S):
0311=このディスクのパーティション全体の削除、そしてこのディスクのデータ全体を消去します。
0312=このパーティションを削除、そしてこのパーティション上のデータ全体を消去します。
0313=このディスクはシステムパーティションを含め、システムパーティションを消去したら、PCが起動できません。この処理を実行してよろしいでしょうか。
0314=パーティション消去回数の指定(&S):

0315=ヘルプのオープンに失败しました。
0316=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/purchase.html?pa
0317=ChengDu AoMei Tech Co., Ltd.
0318=AOMEI Partition Assistantプロ版 (日本語)
0319=AOMEI Partition Assistantサーバ版 (日本語)

0320=AOMEI Partition AssistantはWindows NT/2000/XP/2003/Vista/2008和Windows 7/8の環境で実行しなければなりません。
0321=AOMEI Partition Assistantは実行しています。
0322=AOMEI Partition Assistantは管理者権限で実行しなければなりません。
0323=ドライバーのロードに失败しました。アプリケーションを再インストールまたは再グリーニングしてください。
0324=本製品はWindows安全モードで実行できません。
0325=現在のバージョンはサーバでサポートされていません。AOMEI Partition Assistantサーバ版をご利用ください。
0326=解像度DPIを96(100%)に調整してアプリケーション画面を最適化で表示することをすすめます。
0327=AOMEI Partition Assistant

0328=AOMEI Partition Assistant企業版 (日本語)
0329=AOMEI Partition Assistant標準版 (日本語)
0330=AOMEI Partition Assistant技術者版 (日本語)
0331=AOMEI Partition Assistantプロ版(试用版) (日本語)
0332=AOMEI Partition Assistantサーバ版(试用版) (日本語)
0333=AOMEI Partition Assistantプロ版(试用版) (日本語)
0334=AOMEI Partition Assistantサーバ版(试用版) (日本語)
0335=AOMEI Partition Assistant试用版 (日本語)
0336=AOMEI Partition Assistant簡略版 (日本語)
0337=Copyright (C) 2009-2015 AOMEI Technology Co., Ltd. 版権を所有します。
0338=われわれのウェブサイト:\n\n<u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp">http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/</a></font></u>をアクセスして、最新バージョンのアプリケーションを取得できます。

0339=AOMEI Partition Assistantが処理されるパーティションで実行しています。この処理を実行するには、「PCを再起動」をクリックしてアプリケーションをPreOS(再起動)モードで実行するようにしてください。PCを再起動したくないのであれば、システムパーティション(一般はC:\Program Files)にインストールすることをすすめます。
0340=ローディングディスクを再起動することはパーティションに対する変更処理を破棄することになります。よろしいでしょうか。
0341=http://www.aomeitech.com/jp
0342=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/newsletter.html
0343=ツールバーの「適用」ボタンをクリックして、前の処理を物理ディスクに保存して置いてください。その後、本製品を使って現在の処理を続行できます。
0344=この位置でもっとパーティションを作成できませんので、MBRディスクで2TBを超えたディスクの末尾の領域が利用できません。このディスクをGPTディスクへ変換したら、作成できます。
0345=現在のディスクで既に４つのパーティションがあります。もっとパーティションを作成するには、まずこのディスクにある一つのパーティションを論理パーティションへ変換してください。この精简版は基本・論理パーティション間の変換がサポートされていませんので、この問題を解決するには完全版をご購入ください。
0346=mailto:?subject=なかなか良いディスクパーティション製品: AOMEI Partition Assistant&body=Hello、%0A%0Aこれは良い製品と思います。パーティションのサイズ、ディスクのコピー、パーティションのコピー・作成・削除など多くの機能を持っています。ぜひ試みてください。%0A%0Aは無料で利用できます。http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/free-partition-manager.htmlウェブサイトでダウンロ—ドできます（笑）。
0347=パーティションの拡張ウィザードの実行に失败しました。アプリケーションのインストールディレクトリでこのウィザードを実行してください。
0348=ヘルプのオープンに失败しました。http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/tutorials.htmlウェブサイトをアクセスしてヘルプを取得してください。
0349=PDFユーザーマニュアルのオープンに失败しました。「F1」を押下してヘルプドキュメントをオープンしてください。
0350=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/home-upgrade.html
0351=MBRディスクへ変換
0352=GPTディスクへ変換
0353=論理パーティションへ変換
0354=基本パーティションへ変換

0355=論理パーティションへ変換(&N)
0356=基本パーティションへ変換(&N)
0357=非表示したパーティションを再表示(&H)
0358=MBRディスクへ変換(&O)
0359=GPTディスクへ変換(&O)
0360=現在のディスクでパーティションテーブルが重なるエラーがあります。このエラーを修復しなければなりません。そうでなければ、このパーティションのサイズが調整できません。このエラーを修復してよろしいでしょうか。
0361=パーティションテーブルのエラーを成功に修復しました。修復を有効するには、「確認」をクリックしてPCを再起動してください。
0362=
0363=すみませんが、パーティションテーブルの修復に失败しました。
0364=パーティションの非表示(&H)
0365=適用必要のあるパーティション処理がありますので、アプリケーションを終了する前にこれらの処理を適用しますか。
0366=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/tutorials.html
0367=選択されたディスクのパーティション全体を削除、またはデータ全体を消去します。

0368=アプリケーション起動時に製品アップデート情報をチェック(&C)。
0369=不良セクタのチェック
0370=開始(&S)
0371=クイックチェック(&Q)
0372=正常
0373=不良
0374=ブロックサイズ
0375=チェックスピード:
0376=経過時間:
0377=残り時間:
0378=「開始」ボタンをクリックして、チェックを開始します。
0379=不良セクタのチェック
0380=見つかった不良セクタは下記の通りです:\n
0381=不良セクタ: %I64d\n
0382=チェック中…\n
0383=計算中…
0384=チェックが完了しました。\n
0385=チェックが完了しました。「キャンセル」ボタンをクリックして終了します。\n

0386=winchk.exeの呼び出しの失敗しました。このアプリケーションは本アプリケーションインストールディレクトリ(%s)で見つかりません。
0387=(%c:)をチェックしています。しばらくお待ちください…\n-------------------------------------------------------------\n
0388=パーティションチェック時エラーが発生しました。chkdsk.exeを使ってこのパーティションをチェックしてください。
0389=パーティションのクイック調整

0390=パーティション
0391=ファイルシステム
0392=容量
0393=未使用
0394=種類
0395=使用済
0396=ステータス
0397=ボリューム
0398=ディスク
0399=サイズ
0400=モデル
0401=AOMEI Partition Assistant does not support to manage dynamic disks in a WinPE, but you could manage them in a non-WinPE, such as Windows 7.
0402=簡略版はGPTディスクがサポートされていません。サポートするには、完全版をご購入ください。
0403=ディスクはオフラインステータスで、Windowsディスクマネージャーで切り替えこのディスクをオンラインステータスに切り替えしてから処理を実行してください。
0404=ダイナミックディスク
0405=オフラインディスク
0406=ディスク%d情報
0407=総サイズ: %s
0408=幾何構造: %I64d, %d, %d
0409=使用済: %s
0410=ディスクモデル: %s
0411=パーティションの種類
0412=未割り当て
0413=未フォーマットの
0414=exFAT
0415=EXT2
0416=EXT3
0417=Other
0418=FAT12
0419=FAT16
0420=FAT32
0421=NTFS
0422=不明
0423=パーティションサイズ: %s
0424=ディスク%d (%s)

0425=有料機能
0426=パーティションの調整
0427=フリー領域の割り当て
0428=基本パーティションへ変換
0429=もっと機能
0430=パーティション処理
0431=NTFSパーティションへ変換
0434=ウィザード
0435=パーティションの拡張
0436=ディスクのコピー
0437=パーティションのコピー
0438=パーティションの復元
0439=ディスクのコピー
0440=GPTディスク

0441=ディスク型番:
0442=総结種類:
0443=ディスク署名:
0444=物理総セクタ:
0445=総サイズ:
0446=シリンダー数:
0447=シリンダー毎のトラック数:
0448=トラック毎のセクタ数:

0449=アンリミテッド
0450=セクタ毎のバイト数:
0451=クラスター毎のセクタ数:
0452=ルートディレクトリのセクタ数:
0453=保留するセクタ数:
0454=FATテーブルのセクタ数:
0455=FATテーブルの先頭セクタ:
0456=データエリアの先頭セクタ:

0457=一時パーティション情報
0458=使用済: %s (%.2f%%)
0459=未使用: %s (%.2f%%)

0460=ファイルシステム総セクタ数:
0461=MFTの先頭クラスター番号:
0462=ファイルレコード每のセクタ数:
0463=インデックスブロック每のセクタ数:
0464=NTFSバージョン番号:

0465=ファイルシステム:
0466=先頭セクタ:
0467=末尾のセクタ:
0468=デバイス名:ｂｂ
0469=マウントポイント:

0470=基本
0471=論理
0472=アクティブ
0473=非表示
0474=システム
0475=ブート

0476=ターゲットディスクのレイアウト
0477=サイズを変更せずにコピーします
0478=をディスクのサイズに適応
0479=ィスクのパーティションを調整
0480=コピーオプション

0481=次へ(&N)
0482=
0483=パーティション(%c:)の領域が足りません。「ターゲットディスクのパーティションの編集」オプションを選択して、このパーティションを適当なサイズに調整してください。
0484=ディスクのパーティションを編集
0485=ターゲットディスクのパーティションのサイズと位置が調整できます。
0486=「次へ」をクリックして続きます。

0487=SSDディスクの性能を最適化(&O)(選択されたターゲットディスクがSSDディスクである場合、ここをチェックすることをすすめます)
0488=この処理を適用した後、ターゲットディスクのデータ全体が消去され、パーティション全体が削除されます。よろしいでしょうか。「はい」をクリックして確認し、そして次の画面でターゲットディスクのパーティションを編集できます。
0489=ターゲットディスクを選択
0490=ターゲットディスクを選択して、ソースディスクからターゲットディスクへコピーします。
0491=コピーする過程中ターゲットディスクのパーティション全体が削除されます。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。
0492=ターゲットディスクはダイナミックディスクまたはオフラインステータスのディスクになりません。
0493=システムディスクまたはブートディスクはターゲットディスクになりません。
0494=選択されたディスクはソースディスクです。
0495=選択されたディスクの領域が足りません。最小限の領域サイズ: %s。
0496=クイックコピー方法を試みます

0497=戻る(&B)
0498=完了(&F)
0499=OSのブート
0500=どのようにターゲットディスクのOSを起動できますか。
0501=「完了」ボタンをクリックしてメイン画面に戻ってから、ツールバーの「適用」をクリックしてこの処理を有効にします。
0502=<b>Note:</b><br><br>After clone or migration, all destination disks can boot up perfectly. However, just in few cases, computer may not boot from the destination disk. If you encounter such problem, you can disconnect the source disk from computer, or, exchange the connection socket of destination disk and source disk. Then, boot the computer from destination disk.
0503=ディスクのコピーの方法を選択
0504=適当な方法を選択してディスクのコピーを実行します。
0505=このウィザードはあるディスクを別のディスクへのコピーを案内します。ディスクのクローンとも言います。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。
0506=ディスクの使用領域だけを別のディスクへコピー、そしてコピー時にディスクのパーティションのサイズを調整することが許可します。(おすすめの方法)
0507=セクタが使用されているかどうかにかかわらず、ディスクのセクタ全体をターゲットディスクへコピーします。
0508=クイックディスクのコピー(&C)
0509=セクタからセクタへのコピー(&S)
0510=このウィザードはあるディスクを別のディスクへのコピーを案内します。現在のディスク%dがソースディスクとして選択されています。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。
0511=ディスクのコピー処理
0512=選択されたディスクでパーティションが存在しません。このディスクのコピーはセクタからセクタへの方法で実行します。
0513=ソースディスクを選択
0514=コピーしたいディスクを一つ選択してください。
0515=在ソースディスクのパーティション全体は選択されたターゲットディスクへコピーされます。
0516=ダイナミックディスクとオフラインステータスのディスクはソースディスクになりません。

0517=どのようにOSをSSDまたはHDDディスクから起動しますか
0518=<b>Note:</b><br><br>After clone or migration, all destination disks can boot up perfectly. However, just in few cases, computer may not boot from the destination disk. If you encounter such problem, you can disconnect the source disk from computer, or, exchange the connection socket of destination disk and source disk. Then, boot the computer from destination disk.
0519=内部エラー。
0520=ターゲットパーティションのサイズまたは位置を设定
0521=「次へ」をクリックして、どのようにシステムをSSDディスクから起動することを学びます。
0522=「完了」をクリックしてメイン画面に戻って、ツールバーの「適用」をクリックしてこの処理を有効にします。

0523=SSDディスクの性能を最適化(&O)(選択された未割り当て領域がSSDディスクの一部である場合、ここをチェックすることをすすめます)
0524=選択されたターゲットディスクはGPTディスクです。しかし、アプリケーションは遷移OSをGPTディスクへ遷移するこをができません。GPT以外のディスクを選択して、またはこのGPTディスクをMBRディスクへ変換して再試行してください。
0525=ディスク領域を選択
0526=SSD(フラッシュメモリドライブ)またはHDD(ハードディスクドライブ)である未割り当て領域を選択します。
0527=ターゲット領域を選択
0528=ある未割り当て領域を選択して、コピーしたいパーティションのターゲット領域とします。
0529=選択されたターゲットディスクはダイナミックディスクです。しかし、アプリケーションはOSをダイナミックディスクに遷移できません。AOMEI Dynamic Disk Managerを使って基本ディスクへ変換してから再試行してください。
0530=ある未割り当て領域を選択してください。未割り当て領域がなければ、他のパーティションを縮小または削除して、未割り当て領域を作成できます。
0531=このディスクは4つの基本パーティションがありますので、新しいパーティションがこのディスクへ作成できません。しない基本パーティションを削除または一つの基本パーティションを結合することをすすめます。
0532=このディスクの基本パーティション数は最大限の4つになります。一つの基本パーティションへ論理パーティションに変換して、この遷移処理を再試行してください。
0533=ディスク領域が足りません。最小限の未割り当て領域は: %s。

0534=アプリケーションはダイナミックディスクのOSからSSDまたはHDDディスクへの遷移がサポートされていません。AOMEI Dynamic Disk Managerを使って、基本ディスクへ変換して再試行してください。
0535=アプリケーションはGPTディスクのOSからSSDまたはHDDディスクへの遷移がサポートされていません。
0536=この遷移を実現するには、OSパーティションが少なくとも800MBの空き領域を確保します。
0537=システムをSSDまたはHDDに遷移します。
0538=このウィザードは現在のOSをSSD(フラッシュメモリドライブ)またはHDD(ハードディスクドライブ)への遷移を案内します。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。
0539=パーティションのコピーの方法を選択
0540=適当な方法を選択してパーティションのコピーをします。
0541=このウィザードはパーティションのコピーを案内します。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。
0542=パーティションの使用領域だけをコピーして、そしてコピー時にパーティションのサイズを調整することができます。(おすすめの方法)
0543=セクタが使用されているかどうかにかかわらず、パーティションのセクタ全体を他のディスクへコピーします。
0544=パーティションのクイックコピー(&C)
0545=(%c:) このウィザードはあるパーティションを他のディスクへのコピーを案内します。続行するには、「次へ」ボタンをクリックしてください。
0546=パーティションのコピー処理

0547=選択されたパーティションはセクタからセクタへの方法だけコピーします。
0548=ソースパーティションを選択案内します。
0549=コピーしたいパーティションを選択してください。
0550=コピーしたいパーティションを選択して、ソースパーティションとします。
0551=このウィザードはパーティションのコピーを案内します。現在の選択された(%c:)パーティションをソースパーティションとします。続行するには、「次へ」をクリックしてください。

0552=オフラインディスクは復元できません。Windowsディスクマネージャーを使ってオンラインステータスへ切り替えて、復元できます。
0553=パーティションの復元ウィザードへようこそ
0554=復元したいパーティションにあるディスクを選択してください。
0555=このディスクはもう4つの基本パーティションがありますので、このディスクのパーティションが復元できません。あるパーティションを論理パーティションへ変換して再試行してください。

0556=中止(&P)
0557=選択されたパーティションのファイルを閲覧
0558=検索中。しばらくお待ちください…
0559=失われたパーティションを選択案内します。
0560=下記のリストから復元したいパーティションを選択してください。
0561=選択されたパーティションは存在するパーティションと重なっていますので、もう一度選択してください。
0562=検索が終わりました。復元したいパーティションを選択して、「実行」ボタンをクリックしてください。
0563=パーティションが見つかりませんでした。他の検索方法を選択して失われたパーティションを検索できます。
0564=続く(&C)
0565=アプリケーションは中止しています。「続く」をクリックして、再開できます。あるいはあるパーティションをダブルクリックして、パーティションのファイルを表示できます。
0566=このパーティションが表示できません、アプリケーションはNTFSまたはFAT32パーティションのファイルしか閲覧できません。

0567=アプリケーションはパーティションテーブルを物理ディスクへ書き込んでいます。
0568=パーティションの復元処理を有効するには、PCを再起動する必要があります。「確認」をクリックして再起動します。
0569=おめでとうございます。\n\nパーティションは復元されました。"マイ　コンピューター"でこれらのパーティションを閲覧できます。"マイ　コンピューター"で復元されたパーティションが見えない場合、PCを再起動してから、これらのパーティションにドライブ文字を設定してください。

0570=検索方法を選択案内します。
0571=クイック検索または完全検索を選択できます。
0572=クイック検索(&F)
0573=おすすめの方法。より少ない時間で失われたパーティションを見つけます。この方法で失われたパーティションを見つからない場合、完全検索で検索してください。
0574=完全検索(&F)
0575=この方法はディスクのセクタ全体を検索しますので、時間がかかります。クイック検索でパーティションを見つからない場合、この方法がおすすめます。

0576=適用
0577=破棄
0578=元に戻す
0579=やり直し
0580=リロード
0581=ガイド
0582=完全版を購入
0583=アップデート
0584=パーティション情報
0585=Bitlocker暗号化


0586=元に戻す(Ctrl+Z)
0587=やり直し(Ctrl+Y)
0588=適用 (Ctrl+Enter)
0589=破棄 (Ctrl+D)
0590=リロード (F5)
0591=
0592=終了(&X)
0593=通常(&G)

0594=ディスク(&D)
0595=ディスクのコピー(&C)
0596=ディスクの初期化(&I)
0597=ディスクの消去(&W)
0598=不良セクタのチェック(&S)
0599=MBRのリビルド(&R)
0600=パーティション全体の削除(&D)
0601=MBR/GPTディスクの交換(&M)
0602=プロパティ(&P)

0603=パーティション(&P)
0604=パーティションの調整/移動(&R)
0605=パーティションの移動(&M)
0606=パーティションの結合(&E)
0607=パーティションの分割(&S)
0608=パーティションの空き領域(&A)
0609=パーティションのコピー(&O)
0610=パーティションの作成(&C)
0611=パーティションの削除(&D)
0612=フォーマット(&F)
0613=ボリュームラベルの設定(&L)
0614=パーティションの消去(&W)
0615=詳細処理(&A)
0616=ドライブ文字の変更(&R)
0617=パーティションの非表示(&H)
0618=アクティブパーティションの設定(&S)
0619=NTFSパーティションへ変換(&O)
0620=基本パーティションへ変換(&N)
0621=エラーチェック(&K)
0622=データの消去(&W)
0623=パーティションの種類IDの変更(&T)
0624=パーティションのシリアル番号の変更(&M)
0625=パーティションのアライメント(&P)

0626=ウィザード(&W)
0627=ディスクのコピーウィザード(&D)
0628=パーティションのコピーウィザード(&P)
0629=パーティションの拡張ウィザード(&E)
0630=OSをSSD/HDDへ遷移(&M)
0631=パーティションの復元ウィザード(&R)

0632=ヘルプ(&H)
0633=ドキュメント内容(&C)    F1
0634=ユーザーマニュアル(&M)
0635=新しいバージョンのチェック(&U)
0636=技術サポート(&S)
0637=利用許可アップデート(&L)
0638=友人にすすめます(&T)
0639=オンラインマニュアル(&O)
0640=AOMEI Partition Assistantについて(&A)

0641=購入(&P)
0642=すぐに購入(&B)
0643=Please first click Apply on the toolbar to commit the previous pending operations

0645=%c:でページファイル(Paging File in %c:)が存在していますので、変換する前に一時別の場所に移動し、PCを再起動する必要があります。
0646=パーティション名称:\t\t
0647=パーティションサイズ:\t
0648=增加値:\t\t\t
0649=縮小値:\t\t\t
0650=移動値:\t\t\t
0651=パーティションの拡張
0652=パーティションの縮小
0653=パーティションの移動

0654=新規增加するサイズ
0655=最小サイズ %s
0656=最大サイズ %s
0657=拡張されているパーティションは%s (%c:)。ディスクのパーティション情報は下記の通りです。
0658=ローカルディスク
0659=パーティションに新しいサイズを指定して、「次へ」ボタンをクリックしてください。
0660=このパーティションに少なくとも64MBの領域を増加する必要があります。
0661=縮小できないパーティションがありますので、リストからチェックを外してください。あるいは
0662=パーティションに新しいサイズを指定します。
0663=もう一度パーティションのサイズを指定してください。
0664=パーティションの新しいサイズ(&P)
0665=拡張したいパーティションの新しいサイズを設定します。
0666=パーティションの新しいサイズを設定してください。スクロールバーのドラッグまたは新しいサイズを直接に入力することによって設定できます。
0667=「次へ」をクリックして、処理を確認します。
0668=<font color="#0000f0"><a href="#MESSAGE">ここ</a></font>をクリックして、FAT/FAT32のパーティションの領域を使って、パーティションを拡大します。

0669=试用版ですが、完全版を購入する必要があります。\n\nこの製品が好きな方は、ウェブサイトwww.disk-partition.comをアクセスしてご購入ください。あるいはアプリケーションのメイン画面でツールバーの「購入」ボタンをクリックしてご購入ください。
0670=试用版ですが、完全版を購入する必要があります。\n\nこの製品が好きな方は、アプリケーションのメイン画面に戻って，ツールバーの「購入」ボタンをクリックしてご購入ください。

0671=Windows制御コードを使ってボリュームの拡大に失败しました。AOMEI Partition Assistantメイン画面でこのパーティションを拡大できますので、このエラーの発生を避けます。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0672=すみませんが、処理はキャンセルされました。\r\n情報コード: %d\r\n
0673=ボリュームがロックに失败。AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面でこのパーティションを拡大し、このエラーの发生を避けます。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0674=ヘルプ
0675=選択の拡大
0676=拡大したいパーティションを選択してください。
0677=システムパーティションを拡大します。一般はディスクCを指します。
0678=ディスク
0679=拡張システムパーティション(&E)
0680=下記のディスクから拡張したいパーティションを選択してください(&S)。
0681=これらの処理をキャンセルしてよろしいでしょうか。「はい」をクリックして、アプリケーションは今回処理を実行完了後にすべての処理の実行を終了します。\n\nデータが不整合または失われたことを避けるために、アプリケーションを強制終了しないことをご注意ください。
0682=「完了」ボタンをクリックして、アプリケーションを終了してください。
0683=下記の処理が処理されています。
0684=サブ進捗

0685=本製品をシステムパーティション(一般はC:\Program Filesディレクトリ)にインストールして、このウィザードを使ってパーティションを拡張してください。
0686=これらの処理は時間がかかりますので(約%s)、しばらくお待ちください。今すぐこの処理を実行してよろしいでしょうか。 \n\n注意:アプリケーションは処理されるパーティションで実行するアプリケーションを閉じる可能性がありますので、個別ショートカットが一時無効かもしれませんが、アプリケーションが実行した後、正常に復元することになります。
0687=ディスクのレイアウト
0688=実行される下記の処理を確認してください。
0689=「実行」ボタンをクリックして、このパーティションの拡張を始めます。
0690=下記の項目が実行されます。

0691=リストからあるパーティションを選択して「次へ」をクリックしてください。そうでなければ、アプリケーションはこのディスクの未割り当て領域を使って拡大したいパーティションを拡張します。
0692=続行するには、リストにパーティションを一つ以上選択してください。
0693=FAT32が处理できません。NTFSへ変換してもっと%sの領域を取得できます。
0694=NTFSへ変換するには、PCを再起動する必要があります。今すぐ再起動してよろしいでしょうか。
0695=レジストリの編集失败。この処理がアンチウィルスソフトによって阻止された可能性があります。
0696=パーティションの選択
0697=下記のパーティションを選択して、空き領域を取得します。
0698=下記のパーティションを選択して、パーティションを縮小して、空き領域を作って拡大したいパーティションを拡張します。
0699=「次へ」をクリックして、拡張されるパーティションの新しいサイズを設定します。
0700=上記のパーティションが縮小できない場合、<font color="#0000f0"><a href="#MESSAGE">ここ</a></font>をクリックして、ディスクの未割り当て領域たけでパーティションを拡大します。
0701=%c: ローカルディスク

0702=パーティションの拡張ウィザードを終了しますか。
0703=パーティションの自動拡張モード(&A)
0704=選択されたパーティションを安全でクイックに拡大します。
0705=アプリケーションはディスクがセクタ每のバイト数は512でないことを検出しました。こんな大きなセクタがサポートされていません。
0706=すみませんが、アプリケーションはエラーが発生しまいました。現在のディスクをロードに失败しました。PCを再起動して再試行してください。
0707=このウィザードはGPTディスクのパーティションの拡張がサポートされていません、GPTディスクのパーティションに対する処理は、AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面で実行してください。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0708=アプリケーションは2TBを超えたディスクが処理できません。
0709=拡張されるパーティションはNTFSではありません。NTFSへ変換しますか。「はい」をクリックしたら変換します。「いいえ」をクリックしたら変換しません。変換しない場合、AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面でこのパーティションを拡大できますし、このエラーの发生を避けます。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0710=システムにBitlocker(%c:)暗号化のパーティションが見つかりました。すべての暗号化機能を閉じて、ウィザードが利用できます。AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面で容量を增加したいパーティションを拡大することをすすめます。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0711=種類不明のパーティションが拡張できません。もう一度パーティションを選択してください。
0712=当ウィザードはこのパーティションを拡大できません。AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面でパーティションを拡大してください。
0713=当ウィザードはこのパーティションを拡大できません。AOMEI Partition Assistantのメイン画面でパーティションを拡大してください。詳細情報：http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/pa-extend-partition.html
0714=パーティションの拡張ウィザードへようこそ。このウィザードは気軽くNTFSパーティションの容量拡張処理を案内します。簡単にスクロールバーをドラッグして済みです。

0715=ローディング中…
0716=アプリケーションはディスクデバイスをローディングしています。しばらくお待ちください…
0717=%c:%s\n%s %s\nアイドル:%s
0718=ディスクまたはパーティション情報が変わりました(例えば、システムにUSBメモリーを插入または除去されます)。新しいディスクのパーティションをもう一度ローディングしますか。
0719=(%c:)・パーティション%d・ディスク%dをローディングしています
0720=AOMEI Partition Assistant

0722=AOMEI Partition Assistantについて
0723=基本
0724=ダイナミック

0725=
0726=
0727=

0728=ミニブログ
0729=この製品のスキンを変更しますか。他のスキンに変更するには、「はい」をクリックしてから、この製品を再起動してください。

0730=ブータブルCDの作成
0731=Windows PEのブータブルCDを作成します
0732=The program will help you make a bootable USB drive, Disc or a bootable ISO file.
0733=WinPEのブータブルCDを作成には、Windows AIKをダウンロ—ドしてシステムにインストールして置いてください。あなたのシステムにはWindows AIKがインストールされていませんので、下記のリンクをクリックしてダウンロ—ドしてください。<br><u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/help/winaik.html">Windows AIKのダウンロ—ド</a></font></u>
0734=Windows AIKをインストールしてから、「次へ」をクリックして続行します。
0735=ISOのパスを保存
0736=閲覧(&R)
0737=Please select a way to make the desired bootable media, and then click "Proceed" to start.
0738=システムが起動できないことを避けるために、GPTシステムパーティションの前に、どんなパーティション処理でも実行しないでください。
0739=ダイナミックディスクのパーティションが復元できません。AOMEI Dynamic Disk Managerを使って基本ディスクへ変換して再試行してください。
0740=ReFS
0741=ブータブルCDの作成ウィザード(&A)
0742=ブータブルCDの作成
0743=PCを再起動してください。再起動してから、ブータブルCDのISOファイルが作成できます。
0744=<b>注意:</b> ブータブルISOファイルが作成しました。Nero、UltraISOなどのサードパーティのデータ書き込みツールを使って、ファイル%sをCD/USBメモリーに書き込みできます。
0745=ブータブルISOファイルの作成に失败しました。 The WIM file you specified may be invalid or there might be an error during the process of the creation. We suggest you to reboot computer and try once again, or read online FAQ.
0746=ターゲット位置にファイルが存在していますので、上書きしますか。
0747=アプリケーション実行しています。しばらくお待ちください…
0748=アプリケーションは実行しています。完了まで何分間かかります。しばらくお待ちください。
0749=次回から表示しない(&N)。
0750=登録
0751=シリアル番号
0752=シリアル番号がなければ、<u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/purchase.html?pa">ここ</a></font></u>クリックして購入できます。
0753=登録に成功しました。
0754=この製品を登録して置いてください。
0755=最適化
0756=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/lite.ini
0757=簡略版はインターネット接続が必要があります。インターネットに正常に接続できることを確認してください。
0758=パーティションの調整/移動(&R)
0759=シリアル番号がなければ、http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/をアクセスしてご購入ください。
0760= - 非商用利用のみ無料
0761=設定(&S)
0762=言語(&L)
0763=言語設定
0764=言語
0765=無効なシリアル番号。
0766=メイン画面が表示されている場合、ツールバーの"設定" -> "言語"をクリックして、言語設定を変更できます。
0767=ディスク処理
0768=パーティション処理
0769= - 個人用・商用とも無料

0770=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/buy-pa-pro.html?pa
0771=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/buy-pa-server.html?pa
0772=http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/buy-pa-unlimited.html?pa
0773=WinPEのブータブルCDを作成には、Windows ADKをダウンロ—ドしてシステムにインストールして置いてください。あなたのシステムにはWindows ADKがインストールされていませんので、下記のリンクをクリックしてダウンロ—ドしてください。<br><u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/jp/help/winaik-win8.html">Windows ADKのダウンロ—ド</a></font></u>
0774=You need to first install AOMEI Dynamic Disk Manager to handle this disk or use Dynamic Disk Converter to convert it to basic disk. The installation file is enclosed in the ".zip" file.
0775=The current version does not support dynamic disks, you could use Dynamic Disk Converter to convert it to basic disk or upgrade to AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional Edition to manage dynamic disks.
0776=Windows ADKをインストールしてから、「次へ」をクリックして続行します。
0777=NTFS to FAT32 Converter
0778=Dynamic Disk Converter
0779=Free Backup
0780=http://www.backup-utility.com/free-backup-software.html?from=patoolbar
0789=If your OS is non-server system, we highly suggest you to use another freeware: AOMEI Partition Assistant Standard Edition, which have more features for Windows 7/8/XP/Vista. You can download it at: http://www.disk-partition.com/free-partition-manager.html
0790=The disk is greater than 2TB and some partitions on this disk can not be converted. To complete the conversion, you need to ensure there are only four partitions at most on the disk, and the end sector of the last partition is less than 2TB.
0791=The program is now unable to recover this disk, because the bytes per sector on this disk is greater than 512.
0792=The bytes per sector on the source and the destination disk is not equal, so the program is unable to copy.
0793=<b>Please Note:</b><br><br>When the copy disk operation is finished, we suggest you to disconnect/unplug the source disk from your mainboard and reboot your computer. If there are not drive letters, you can use AOMEI Partition Assistant or Windows Disk Management Snap-in to manually assign a drive letter for each partition on the destination disk.
0794=Confirm the operation by clicking Finish
0795=There are too many primary partitions on the disk. You need to convert one of them to logical partition, then the program will support for convert the disk to GPT. To solve the problem, you could also <a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/help/faq.html"><font color="#0000ff">read FAQ</font></a>.
0796=\r\nChkdsk has completed successfully.\n
0797=\r\nChkdsk has completed, but found some errors in the partition.\nYou could use AOMEI Partition Assistant to fix it.\n
0798=Check partition and fix errors in this partition by using chkdsk.exe
0799=Checking  (%c:) and fix it when there are some errors, please wait a few minutes...\n-------------------------------------------------------------\n

0800=Windows To Go Creator
0801=Select a USB drive
0802=Select Windows 8/10 installation file
0803=&Browse
0804=&Proceed
0805=&Cancel
0806=Windows 8/10 to Go
0807=Create a bootable USB drive and allow you to boot Windows 8/10 from this USB drive.
0808=Are you sure you want to cancel?
0809=Information
0810=Please plug a USB drive to your computer first then click Refresh.
0811=Please select a Windows 8/10 installation file.
0812=The Windows 8/10 installation file does not exist in this USB drive, we suggest you to copy the file to other path and retry.
0813=To continue, the program will delete all data on this USB drive and format it. If there are some important data on it, we suggest you to first backup it (use backup tool like free AOMEI Backupper) and retry.
0814=Invalid Windows 8/10 installation file, the program cannot recognize it. Please make sure that it is a Windows 8/10 installation file and select a correct WIM, ESD or ISO file.
0815=Are you sure you want to exit the wizard?
0816=Exiting...
0817=Cancelling, please wait...
0818=Extracting the WIM file...
0819=Failed to extract the ISO file. To solve the problem, first we suggest you to read the tutorial "Learn how to create Windows 8/10 bootable USB drive". And, we suggest you using ISO mounting tools such as Daemon Tools Lite to mount the ISO file as a virtual drive and try again.
0820=Failed to extract the ISO file, you can manually extract "install.wim" from this ISO file or read the tutorial "Learn how to create Windows 8/10 bootable USB drive".
0821=
0822=Formatting partition...
0823=Failed to format,
0824=Setup failed!
0825=The program is creating Windows 8/10 bootable USB drive...
0826=The operation completed successfully.
0827=OK
0828=Select a USB drive on which you want to create a bootable media.
0829=
0830=No USB drive found, please plug in a USB device.
0831=
0832=The selected USB drive is not a primary partition, you need to convert it to primary partition first by using AOMEI Partition Assistant Paid Edition, and try again.
0833=The USB drive capacity is too small, it should be at least 13GB of capacity.
0834=Select Windows 8/10 installation file or click the Browse button to select.
0835=Installation File
0836=Refresh
0837=Please plug a USB drive in your computer first.
0838=Does not support GPT removable device.
0839=Sorry, the USB drive does not have a drive letter at this moment, you need to assign a drive letter by using AOMEI Partition Assistant first, and try again.
0840=
0841=Don't support bitlocker drive.
0842=<font color="#000080"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/wintogo.html?pa">Learn how to create Windows 8/10 bootable USB drive?</a></font>
0843=Windows 8/10 Installation File
0844=Remain Time

1001=If you have installed Windows AIK/ADK in your system, you need to find the WIM file under the installed directory of AIK or ADK, and manually set the file path into the following box.
1002=Burn to CD/DVD
1003=USB Boot Device
1004=Export ISO File
1004=Export ISO File
1005=There's no writable disc in the burner, please insert a writable disc.\nClick "Yes" to continue, or "No".
1006=Detects that there are some data in the specified disc, and this disc doesn't support erasion.\nPlease insert another disc.
1007=Detects that there are some data in the specified disc, they will be erased when burning the bootable disc.\nClick "Yes" to continue, or "No".
1008=we suggest you to backup your important data on this disk, then re-run this operation.
1009=You must choose an item that you want to create the bootable media on. 
1010=The operation will cause that your USB disk%d (%s) is formatted, 
1011=Are you sure you want to format this disk now?
1012=Succeed in creating this USB bootable device.\nNow, you can use this USB device to boot your computer.
1013=All have finished successfully!\n
1014=No supported burner devices
1015=No supported USB devices
1016=The program is loading drive...
1017=You need to install Windows AIK/ADK, or specify the path of the WIM file.

1050=This computer needs to be restarted to complete this operation. Are you sure you want to restart now? In order not to skip the operation, please don't press any key during the process of restart.
1051=Check and Fix Partition
1052=The program found some errors in the partition, would you like to fix it now?
1053=Fixing, please wait...
1054=The operation has completed successfully.
1055=Failed to dismount the partition. To solve the problem and finish the operation, the computer needs to be restarted, are you sure you want to restart now? To prevent skipping the operation, don't press any key during the process of restart.
1056=Check partition timeout, the partitions may have some errors, we suggest you to read: http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/checktimeout.html, or uncheck the "Check partitions before execution" option in the "Pending Operations" window and retry.
1057=Partition checking, please wait...
1058=C&heck partitions before execution
1059=&Automatically fix it when find errors
1060=The program found some errors on the partition, would you like to fix it now? You can click "Fix it" to repair and continue the next operation, or click "Don't fix it" to abort the current operation. If you need to get more detailed information about repairing the errors, please visit at: http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/fixit.html.
1061=&Fix it
1062=&Don't fix it
1063=The program found some errors on the partition, you could right-click the partition in Partition Assistant, and select "Advanced" -> "Check Partition" to fix it. If you need to get more detailed information about repairing the errors, please visit at: http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/fixit.html.
1064=The program is repairing the errors on the partition.
1065=Since there may be a Linux OS on this disk, the rebuild MBR operation could cause the operating system on this disk to not boot. If the disk does not contain a Linux system or a dual-boot system of Windows and Linux, we suggest you to choose to rebuild the disk. Are you sure you want to rebuild MBR for this disk?
1066=The disk may contain a Linux system or a dual-boot system of Windows and Linux. To make your system bootable, please do not create new partitions or delete partitions before the Linux system partition. However, the current operation may cause your system to not boot, so we suggest you not to continue this operation. If the disk does not contain a Linux system or a dual-boot system of Windows and Linux, please click Yes. Otherwise, you could click No. 
1067=Some files (Windows\Boot\EFI\bootmgfw.efi, Windows\Boot\EFI\bootmgr.efi or Windows\Boot\PCAT\bootmgr) were not found in your system, so the operation will be unable to continue.
1068=The file (2Gpt_BCD or 2Mbr_BCD) may be lost, we suggest you to reinstall AOMEI software and try again.
1069=The operation has been completed successfully, now please reboot the computer for the operation to take effect. Click OK to reboot.
1070=The system partition and boot partition are separated on different disks. If you convert the disk, your system will be unable to boot next time. So we strongly suggest you not to convert this disk. Do you still want to convert it?
1071=Note: are you sure you want to put Windows 8 system on your USB drive? If so, you could use the tool "Windows To Go Creator" in AOMEI Partition Assistant to realize it. Windows To Go is better than Windows PE. Of course, you can also use the wizard to create a Windows PE bootable media first.
1072=Since this selected disk is a system or boot disk, before converting it to GPT disk, please make sure if your motherboard supports EFI/UEFI boot(read motherboard's user manual). If not, please don't convert it to GPT disk, otherwise your system will be unable to boot next time. Would you like to convert it?
1073=The current version, AOMEI Partition Assistant Standard Edition does not support the conversion of system disk between MBR and GPT style. To realize this operation, we suggest you to upgrade to Professional Edition. Please visit the edition comparison page for more information: <u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html?gptmbrconversion">http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html</a></font></u>
1074=The current version, AOMEI Partition Assistant Lite Edition does not support the conversion of system disk between MBR and GPT style. To realize this operation, we suggest you to upgrade to Server Edition. Please visit the edition comparison page for more information: <u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/get-full.html?gptmbrconversion">http://www.disk-partition.com/get-full.html</a></font></u>
1075=Sorry, the selected disk is a GPT disk, but the current version, AOMEI Partition Assistant Standard Edition does not support the migration of OS to GPT disk. To realize this operation, we suggest you to upgrade to Professional Edition. Please check the edition comparison page for more information: <u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html?togptmigration">http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html</a></font></u>
1076=Sorry, your OS is located on a GPT disk, but the current version, AOMEI Partition Assistant Standard Edition does not support this operation. To realize this function, we suggest you to upgrade to Professional Edition. Please visit the edition comparison page for more information: <u><font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html?gptmigration">http://www.disk-partition.com/home-upgrade.html</a></font></u>

1077=The program does not allow you to put Windows 8 on a flash drive in Windows XP system. We suggest you to use Windows To Go Creator in Windows 7/8 system.
1078=Registering, please wait a few seconds...
1079=Windows 32bit system does not work on a GPT disk, so this disk can not be converted to GPT style. We suggest you to upgrade your system to 64bit.
1080=This 64bit program only supports for Windows PE system, does not support to run on the current system.
1081=<u><b><font color="#eeeeee"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/safely-partition.html?pa">Learn how to safely partition hard drive?</a></font></b></u>
1082=Safely Partition
1083=http://www.disk-partition.com/safely-partition.html?pa
1084=Windows Command Line

1085=After completing copy the system partition, to your system bootable from the destination disk, we highly suggest that you use the "Migrate OS to SSD or HDD" feature to realize copying the system partition to the destination disk. Would you like to cancel the "Copy Partition" feature and run the system migration feature?
1086=

1087=\r\n\r\nWhat does the Information Code mean? Please refer to: http://www.disk-partition.com/help/errorcode.html 
1088=&I want to delete all partitions on this disk %d to migrate system to the disk.
1089=If you do not want to delete all partitions on the selected disk, we suggest you selecting an unallocated space for the migration. If there's no unallocated space, you can click <font color="#0000f0"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/unallocated.html?pa">here</a></font> for more information.
1090=All partitions on the destination disk%d will be deleted during the migration, are you sure to delete them?

1098=Keep the format of the destination disk consistent with the source disk (both are GPT format)
1099=Create a simple Windows PE.
1100=Create a Windows PE that contains Windows Desktop and Start Menu.
1101=To create Windows PE with Windows Desktop and Start Menu, need you to use AOMEI PE Builder to finish. You can download and use this free tool at: 
1102=http://www.aomeitech.com/pe-builder.html
1103=It's strongly recommended to backup important data by using <u><font color="#0000ff"><a href="http://www.backup-utility.com/free-backup-software.html?from=pa">free AOMEI Backupper</a></font></u> before resizing partitions.

1110=Unable to perform "Quick Partition" on a disk that contains either operating system or boot partition. Such operation is only available under Windows PE environment.
1111=Unable to perform "Quick Partition" on a dynamic disk or Offline disk. It suggests that convert the dynamic disk to basic disk with AOMEI Dynamic Disk Converter and try again. 
1112=Unable to perform "Quick Partition" since no disk was found in current system.
1113=Sectors 
1114=GPT
1115=MBR
1116=Partition Count 
1117= Partitions
1118=Tips: You can press "1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 or 9" key to quickly select partition count.
1119=Disk Type
1120=Rebuild MBR
1121=Align Partitions:
1122=Preview Layout
1123=Label:
1124=Default Size
1125=Clear All Labels 
1126=Warnings: After performing, all the existing partitions on current disk will be deleted. Press "Enter" to start partitioning.
1127=Directly enter into "Quick Partition" window next time when you run the software.
1128=Start Partitioning
1129=Quick Partition
1130=System
1131=Software
1132=Docs
1133=Fun
1134=Work
1135=Backup
1136=Videos
1137=Games
1138=Data
1139=Others
1140=Preset
1141=A disk smaller than 10GB is not supported.
1142=For the convenience of partitioning, you can preset default count and size.
1143=The profile (part.ini) of this Preset will be saved to the root directory of all removable devices.
1144=Auto
1145=Remove all volume labels.
1146=Save Settings
1147=Settings have been saved successfully.
1148=Enable Preset
1149=
1150=
1151=Partition Count:\t
1152=Disk Size:\t
1153=Disk Serial Number:\t
1154=Try to assign a drive letter
1155=Quick Partition
1156=This version of AOMEI Partition Assistant is especially designed for being used in Windows PE system. It is not recommended to use it in current Windows system. You can download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional from disk-partition.com and use it in current Windows system.
1157=Warnings：After clicking "Yes", the program will execute "Quick Partition" immediately, and then all the existing partitions on current disk will be deleted. Are your sure you want to click "Yes"?
1158=Unable to perform "Quick Partition" since no disk available to partition was found in current system. To fix this problem, we suggest you install AOMEI Partition Assistant on the system partition (C: drive) or run AOMEI Partition Assistant Bootable Media from USB flash drive. 
1159=Unable to perform "Quick Partition" on the disk where the program is installed. To fix this problem, we suggest you install AOMEI Partition Assistant on the system partition (C: drive) or run AOMEI Partition Assistant Bootable Media from USB flash drive.
1160=Preset is unusable since no removable disk or USB flash drive that can save profile was found. Would you like to boot into Windows PE from physical machine CD or virtual machine ISO? It suggests that boot into Windows PE from USB flash drive to make Preset available.

1161=Incorrect file system.\n
1162=This parameter cannot be recognized.\n
1163=\n[/letter]Incorrect drive letter.\n
1164=Specified size invalid.\n
1165=Removable Disk
1166=Name
1167=Number
1168=Letter
1169=Volume Label
1170=\nLoading, please wait...\n\n
1171=Please format the partitions beyond 4GB to NTFS or FAT32.
1172=Computer will reboot in 30 secs. Press Ctrl+C to quit or add /q to reboot immediately. Countdown:
1173=It will be executed in 30 secs. Press Ctrl+C to quit or add /q to neglect it. Countdown:
1174=The operation is in process. Please do not shut down or reboot the computer, nor forcibly terminate the program!
1175=Incorrect parameter. Unable to find the partitions or disks that need to be operated.
1176=A logical partition cannot be set as active partition.
1177=Incorrect parameter. You may not input disk number, partition number or drive letter.
1178=The file system you entered is incorrect.
1179=Please format the partitions beyond 2TB to NTFS.
1180=The parameter you entered is incorrect.
1181=No unallocated space available to create partitions was found on the disk. It suggests that use "/size:auto" to specify the size.
1182=The partition you want to create is too large. There is not enough unallocated space on this disk (or the /offset value you specified is incorrect). It suggests that use "/size:auto" to specify the size.
1183=Offset value you entered is incorrect.
1184=The specified size of the partition you want to create is incorrect. It suggests that use "/size:auto" to specify the size.
1185=The size of partition being created should be larger than 20MB.
1186=Only logical partitions can be created on this disk, please remove "/pri" parameter.
1187=The drive letter has been assigned to other partition, please re-assign another unused one.
1188=Unable to create the back end partition since there is already a partition at the end of the disk.
1189=There is no need to re-hide the partition or unhide it.
1190=The "/offset" and "/end" cannot both be present, please remove one of them.
1191=Please specify the correct value for "/offset".
1192=There is no longer unallocated space behind the partition.
1193=There is not enough unallocated space behind the partition.
1194=Only partitions formatted with NTFS and FAT32 file systems can be resized without data loss. If the partition is FAT16, please use "convert.exe" to convert FAT16 to NTFS without data loss and then resize it.
1195=After extending the partition, it will exceed 2TB, which is the maximum size of FAT32 file system.
1196=After moving or extending the partition, the end of the partition will exceed the 2TB limit boundary. It suggests that use "/extend:left" or "/right:auto" parameter. 
1197=There is no longer unallocated space before the partition.
1198=The distance moved is too great while the unallocated space is insufficient. It suggests that use "/left:auto" or "/right:auto" parameter to specify the size, or specify a smaller size.
1199=Please visit www.disk-partition.com/help/cmd.html or view User Manual to learn how to use AOMEI Partition Assistant Command Line.
1200=When shrinking a partition, pleased leave more free space for it (at least 30MB, but usually it has to be more than 30 MB so that the shrinking can be successful).
1201=Before initializing a disk, please delete all the partitions on it.
1202=Unable to operate dynamic disks or Offline disks.
1203=Build ESP/MSR Parts
1204=The source path you entered cannot be accessed.
1205=Copying files, please wait...
1206=Copying files is complete.
1207=Copying files error. It may be caused by incorrect destination path or insufficient space.
1208=Cannot assign a drive letter to a hidden partition.
1209=If the process of the "System updating" waits more than 3 minutes, \nyou can forcibly terminate the program by Task Manager.\n
1210=A&dd Drivers
1211=D&elete
1212=Status
1213=Type
1214=Description
1215=To ensure that the PE is more compatible, following detected devices could be added to PE. If a device needn't to be added, please uncheck the option.
1216=The program will run the default operation after %d seconds.
1217=Driver Name
1218=Driver Path
1219=You can add one or more drivers to Windows PE in order to recognize hardware devices in your computer.
1220=The program detected that the disk signature of disk%d is equal to the disk signature of disk%d, which will affect the validity of disk operation. Please remove one of them from your computer and continue. 
1226=It can’t continue to work without power connected or power is less than 70%. Please do it again after connecting power.
1227=Now the computer is not connected to power. In case of making mistake in partitioning due to power off, you are suggested to connect the computer to power before carrying out. Do you want to continue this operation?
1228=There is not enough reserved space on the disk, please choose another method to clone.
1229=Failed to create boot partition, please use CHKDSK to check partitions on the disk and try again. For more help, please refer to FAQ.
1230=There is not enough space on the destination disk, please choose a larger disk as destination location.
1231=Due to current system is 32-bit version, it may be unable to boot after being cloned to destination disk. Do you want to continue?
1232=Due to there are multiple boots on the source disk, it ensures only current system is able to boot after being cloned.
1233=Due to the operating system before Windows Vista (e.g. Windows XP/2003) is not well compatible with GPT disk, we suggest you use Partition Assistant to convert the destination disk to MBR and then continue to clone.
1234=http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/pa-note.html
1235=<font color="#4d4b4b"><a href="http://www.disk-partition.com/lib/boot-computer.html">How to boot computer from destination disk?</a></font>
1236=Can not clone to the destiniation disk due to the partition struct of the source disk. We suggest you keeping that the type (MBR or GPT) of the destination disk is the same as the source disk, or delete the useless non-NTFS or non-FAT32 partitions on the source disk and try again.

;N2F language
2000=&About...
2001=Are you sure to exit the AOMEI Ntfs2Fat32 Converter?
2002=NTFS Partition List
2003=Please select the NTFS partition that you want to convert to FAT32 below.
2004=Please click Next to analyze <b>the %c: partition</b>.
2005=The drive (%c:) is analysing, please wait...
2006=NTFS Features Note
2007=You should process the following files before you convert it to FAT32.
2008=There are some NTFS files that can not be stored in a FAT32 partition in the list box.
2009=Welcome Ntfs2Fat32
2010=Convert to FAT32 from NTFS and vice versa.
2011=Total Progress:
2012=AOMEI NTFS to FAT32 Converter (Ntfs2Fat32) is specifically designed to convert the file system from NTFS to FAT32 without loss of data and vice versa.
2013=Please note that the following NTFS files can not be supported by FAT32:\n1. Compressed Files.\n2. Encrypted Files.\n3. Large Files Over 4GB.\n\nIf the partition contains these files, you should decompress, decrypt these related files and split the large files than 4GB into multiple small files before converting to FAT32. Otherwise, these files will lose after converting.
2014=You could use the following way to process the large files.\n1. Move the large files to another NTFS partition.\n2. Split these large files into multiple small files by using some tools.\n3. Delete the unwanted large files manually.\n\nThe large files over 4GB can not be converted and placed in the FAT32 partition, so you have to deal with them before converting to FAT32.
2015=The files are decrypting, please wait...
2016=The files are decompressing, please wait...
2017=Please decrypt the following files manually.
2018=To avoid data loss, please must process the NTFS feature files that cannot be converted.
2019=Please decompress the following files manually.
2020=Sorry, the converter cannot convert the NTFS partition that is great than 2TB.
2021=Confirm Operation
2022=Please review if you'd like to convert the following NTFS partition to FAT32.
2023=Click the Proceed button to start the conversion.
2024=There are some errors in the NTFS filesystem, please fix the issues with "chkdsk.exe /f".
2025=Are you sure to cancel this conversion?
2026=Are you sure to ignore these files? If do, these files will lost after converting.
2027=
2028=Not enough disk space, please delete some files on the NTFS partition to get more free space.
2029=Please click Finish to return the first page, click Cancel to exit.
2030=The operation has been completed successfully!
2031=<font color="#0000ff"><a href="http://www.aomeitech.com">http://www.aomeitech.com</a></font>
2032=AOMEI NTFS to FAT32 Converter
2033=Copyright (C) 2009-2015 AOMEI Tech Co., Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
2034=Note: After clicking Proceed, the program will check/repair the errors on the partition automatically, when completing the check, the conversion operation will start. In addition, the partition can not be accessed when converting it.
2035=Are you sure to execute the conversion operation?
2036=
2037=There are not NTFS partitions found in your system!
2038=Sorry, the system partition %c: can not be supported for converting to FAT32 yet!
2039=
2040=Click the BuyNow to purchase the full edition, and click the Proceed to test the conversion.
2041=AOMEI NTFS to FAT32 Converter is being run!
2042=AOMEI NTFS to FAT32 Converter can only work under administrator privileges!
2043=
2044=
2045=To ensure the interface appearance, we recommend that you adjust the DPI to 96(100%).
2046=The program detected there is a Paging File (pagefile.sys) on the %c:, please first remove temporarily the Paging File from %c: and reboot computer, then retry. \n\nRemove Method: \nRight click "Computer" -> "Properties" -> "Advanced system settings" -> "Performance Settings" -> "Advanced" -> "Virtual Memory Change".
2047=There are some programs that is running on the partition that need to be converted, would you like to close them?
2048=Sorry, failed to close the programs and dismount the partition If your firewall or anti-virus is running on the partition, please uninstall them and retry.
2049=To take effect, the computer need to be restarted, please click OK to reboot.
2050=Failed to reboot the computer, please do the restart operation manually.
2051=FAT Partition List
2052=Please click Next to confirm <b>the %c: partition</b>.
2053=Select the FAT/FAT32 partition that you want to convert to NTFS below.
2054=There are not FAT and FAT32 partitions found in your system!
2055=Please review if you'd like to convert the following partition to NTFS.
2056=The operation has been cancelled!
2057=The program is working, please wait...
2058=This computer needs to restart to convert this partition to NTFS now. Are you sure to restart immediately? If click No, it will be converted the next time reboot. 
2059=Failed to restart your computer, please manually restart!
2060=
2061=Shut down the computer after completing the conversion.

2062=Start to &decompress these compressed files
2063=H&ow to process the large files over 4GB?
2064=Start to d&ecrypt s these encrypted files
2065=Ignore these files that cannot be converted.

2066=The program is converting FAT/FAT32 to NTFS, please wait...
2067=The program is converting it to FAT32, please wait...
2068=Elapsed Time: %02d:%02d:%02d

2069=Partitions Loading, Please Wait...
2070=Convert Ntfs to Fat32 without losing data.
2071=Safely convert Fat or Fat32 to Ntfs.

2072=About
2073=OK

2075=Analysing
2076=Report
2077=File Decryption
2078=File Decompression


2081=B&uyNow


2084=&NTFS to FAT32
2085=&FAT32 to NTFS

2086=Progress: %I64d/%I64d
2087=Compressed Files
2088=Encrypted Files
2089=Large files over 4GB
2090=Convert FAT/FAT32 to NTFS\n\n\tDrive Letter: %c\n\tLabel: %s\n\tTotal Size: %s\n\nThe program is ready to convert the %c: partition to NTFS.

2092=Convert NTFS to FAT32\n\n\tDrive Letter: %c\n\tLabel: %s\n\tTotal Size: %s\n\nThe program is ready to convert the %c: partition to FAT32.
2093=Convert NTFS to FAT32\n\n\tDrive Letter: %c\n\tLabel: %s\n\tTotal Size: %s\n\n
2094=Unknown Error.
2105=The operation already being canceled.
2137=Invalid file system when convert FAT to NTFS.
2138=Fail in the process of converting FAT to NTFS.
2139=Fail in the process of converting FAT to NTFS. Please reboot to retry.
2140=Error in FAT file system. Please amend it before retry.
2141=Please release more free space before converting from FAT to NTFS.
2142=Unknown error in the process of converting FAT to NTFS.
2161=There is a unknown error during the conversion.
2162=Not enough disk space!
2167=Status: %d/%d
2168=Ntfs2Fat32
2169=We are sorry, the current program has occurred unknown error! Under the installation directory of the program have a called \"log\" folder and a Crash.dmp file, please send them to support@aomeitech.com to get help, thanks!
2171=Succeed in converting it to NTFS.
2175=Failed to convert due to not enough disk space. Please release more free space before converting from FAT to NTFS.
2178=Unused
2179=Check/Repair
2180=Checking and repairing, please wait...
2181=Check and repair the partition before converting it.

;DDC language
3000=This wizard will help you convert dynamic disk back to basic disk without losing data, in order to make your hard disks can be managed more effectively.
3003=Please click <b>Next</b> to continue.
3004=The current product is a demo version and it could not complete the conversion. You can verify whether it is able to work on your computer and recognize your dynamic disk. If you are satisfied with the product, you could click the following "Buy Now" button or the link: <u><font color="#0000c0"><a href="http://www.dynamic-disk-converter.com/buynow.html">www.dynamic-disk-converter.com</a></font></u> to purchase a full version.
3005=Dynamic Disk List
3006=Please select the dynamic disks that you want to convert to basic disk in the following list.
3007=Click <b>Next</b> to check this conversion.
3008=click <b>Proceed</b> to start, the process only take 3-10 seconds.
3009=Confirm Operation
3010=Please review the conversion operation and confirm it.
3011=Are you sure to exit Dynamic Disk Converter %s?
3012=&I have decided to execute this operation, 
3013=The disk layout after conversion, some volumes will lose
3014=The disk layout before conversion
3015=Please Note: Some volumes will lose when converting, so the program can not convert this disk. You could download Aomei Dynamic Disk Manager, or email to support@aomeitech.com to seek help.\r\n\r\nIf you want to convert a Spanned, Striped and RAID-5 volume to basic partition, please use Method 2 to convert them. For detailed info, check FAQ.
3016=Program does not detect any dynamic disk in your system.
3017=Click <b>Finish</b> to restart this computer to take effect.
3018=This computer needs to restart immediately, click OK to reboot!
3019=The computer is restarted fail, please reboot manually!
3020=Dynamic Disk Converter have detected system configuration has changed, \nplease restart the computer to make configuration to take effect, and run Dynamic Disk Converter again. \n\nWould you like to restart this computer? \nClick Yes to restart immediately, click No you need to restart manually.
3021=Failed to load driver, please reinstall Dynamic Disk Converter or contact us.
3022=<b>This is demo version of Dynamic Disk Converter.</b>
3023=Please click the <b>Buy Now</b> button to buy the full version on website <u><font color="#0000c0"><a href="http://www.dynamic-disk-converter.com/buynow.html">www.dynamic-disk-converter.com</a></font></u>.
3024=You are attempting to run the product on a server workstation platform. \nPlease note that the current version can not be run on the server. \nIf you wish to use it on a server, please purchase server version of \nour software on website www.dynamic-disk-converter.com.
3025=After the conversion is complete and reboot, Disk Management will show an extra "Missing Disk" is as follows, please see the FAQ about how to deal with the Missing Disk.
3026=The capacity of the disk selected is above 2TB, and now does not been supported. 
3027=Does not support the disk which is less than 2GB.
3028=For the latest product information, please visit us:\n\n                     <u><font color="#0000c0"><a href="www.dynamic-disk-converter.com">www.dynamic-disk-converter.com</a></font></u>
3029=Copyright (C) 2009 Aomei Technology Co., Ltd. \nAll Rights Reserved.
3030=We are sorry for loading driver to fail.\r\nYou could solve the problem by disabling driver signing. \r\n\r\nMethod 1: \r\nPlease reboot your computer and press F8 to enter advanced boot options, and then select the "Disable Driver Signature Enforcement" to boot system, after login Windows, Dynamic Disk Converter will be able to run normally.\r\n\r\nMethod 2: \r\nInstall free ReadyDriver software and boot system from it. You can download it at: http://www.citadelindustries.net/readydriverplus/index.php
3031=To ensure the interface appearance, we recommend that you adjust the DPI to 96(100%) or 120(125%). 
3032=This disk is offline, please switch to it online by using the Windows Disk Management first.
3033=The selected disk is a foreign/invalid dynamic disk, please first import it by using Windows Disk Management, \nand then restart Dynamic Disk Converter to try again.
3034=Pick a method and click <b>Next</b> to continue.
3035=Select Operation
3036=According to individual circumstance to select a suitable method for the conversion.
3037=Safely, directly and time-saving revert a dynamic disk back to basic disk without losing data.
3038=Sector by sector clone simpled volume, spanned volume, striped volume, mirrored volume and RAID-5 volume from dynamic to basic.
3039=Select Source Volume
3040=Please select a dynamic volume that you want to clone to basic disk below.
3041=Select a dynamic volume and click <b>Next</b> to continue.
3042=Select Destination
3043=Please select an unallocated space being able to accommodate the size of the source volume.
3044=Select an <b>unallocated space</b> and click <b>Next</b> to continue.
3045=Program does not detect any dynamic volume in your system.
3046=The selected disk is a GPT disk, please first convert it to MBR disk by using Windows Disk Management.
3047=There is not a basic disk in your system, so the dynamic volume can't be cloned to basic partition by using the Method 2. \n\nYou can first install a new hard disk as basic disk in your computer, then use this basic disk to complete this conversion.
3048=There aren't any basic disks which were found, so using Method 2 can't complete your conversion.
3049=This dynamic disk is offline, please switch to it online by using the Windows Disk Management first, \nand then restart Dynamic Disk Converter and try again.
3050=The disk is a foreign/invalid dynamic disk, please import it by using Windows Disk Management.
3051=Currently the bootable system volume can't be converted from dynamic to basic partition by using Method 2 yet; you can try to use Method 1 to complete the conversion of your system volume.
3052=Your selected volume can not be accessed, perhaps it was locked by other programs.
3053=Read DBR to fail, perhaps on the disk have some bad sectors.
3054=There are some unknown errors on the volume, for the data security and it can't be converted!
3055=This is an unknown volume which only be converted to a basic partition only by using sector to sector mode.
3056=The selected unknown volume can't be converted to a basic partition.
3057=The program detects the following dynamic volumes will lose after the disk be converted to basic:\n\n
3058=\nIf the disk contains mirrored volume, please back to the previous page and tick at the "Check here if the selected disk contains mirrored volumes (RAID1)" option. \n\nIn addition, because the Method 1 could not directly convert spanned, striped and RAID5 to basic partition, you could use Method 2 to clone these volumes to basic disk. See FAQ for more info.
3059=The one choosed not to meet the requirements, must select an <b>unallocated space</b> greater than %s.
3060=The selected unallocated space is able to accommodate the source dynamic volume, please click <b>Next</b>.
3061=The capacity of the unallocated space is <b>too small</b>, please select a larger than %s.
3062=Program does not detect any available unallocated space on your basic disk. You must have an unallocated space which is able to accommodate the size of the source dynamic volume. \n\nYou could first install a new hard disk as basic disk to system, then use this basic disk to complete this conversion.
3063=Please confirm and click <b>Proceed</b> to continue.
3064=Confirm Operation
3065=Please confirm the following dynamic volume whether needs to be converted to a basic.
3066=Are you sure to abort this conversion?
3067=In order to copy the data faster, we recommend you to choose a space more than %s. \nOf course, you may not to do so.
3068=In the disk has four primary partitions, so other partition can not be created here. \nPlease choose another place.
3069=The software can't be run under Vista/2008/Windows 7/8/8.1 safe mode.
3070=The current product is a demo version and it could not complete the conversion. You can verify whether it is able to work on your computer and recognize your dynamic disk. If you are satisfied with the product, you could visit the link: http://www.dynamic-disk-converter.com to purchase a full version.
3071=Please click the <b>Buy Now</b> button to buy the full version on website http://www.dynamic-disk-converter.com.
3072=The program have detected system configuration has changed, we suggest you restart your computer first.
3073=You must be aware: this disk is a empty disk, after this disk is converted to basic disk, all data on this disk will lose and the disk will become an unallocated space! Are you sure to convert it?
3074=This selected disk is GPT style, this program can not handle GPT dynamic disks. You could download Aomei Dynamic Disk Manager from http://www.dynamic-disk.com to convert it, or email to support@aomeitech.com to get help.
3075=All operations have been completed, please click OK to restart the computer in order to take effect the conversion operations.
3076=You need to buy one copy of AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional Edition for the conversion. Thanks!
3077=You need to buy one copy of AOMEI Partition Assistant Server Edition for the conversion. Thanks!
3078=AOMEI Dynamic Disk Converter
3079=Dynamic Disk Converter can only be run under Windows 2000/XP/2003/Vista/2008, Windows 7/8 and more higher versions.
3080=Dynamic Disk Converter is being run!
3081=Dynamic Disk Converter can only be run under administrator privileges.


3085=Buy &Later
3086=Demo Version

3088=The conversion operation has been completed successfully!
3089=There is a error occurred during this conversion. (Info Code:%d)
3090=Click the <b>Finish</b> button to exit
3091=&FAQ
3092=Load dirver to fail
3093=Mirrored volume is being loaded, please wait...
3094=Please waiting, converting...
3095=Current Operation Progress
3096=Automatically shutdown the computer after the completion.
3097=Converting...
3098=Processing

3105=&Check here if the selected disk contains mirrored volumes (RAID1).
3106=Method 1
3107=Method 2
3108=C&onvert a dynamic disk back to basic disk
3109=Co&nvert any dynamic volume to basic partition

3110=Sorry, the program can not continue! In the installation directory of the program have a called \"log\" folder, Crash.dmp and LdmData.dmp file, please send them to support@dynamic-disk.com to get help, thanks!
3111=Open help to fail!
3112=please tick at here
3113=\n\nThe version is demo edition, please purchase one copy of full version for the conversion. The full version can complete the conversion process within 3~10 seconds.\n
3114=The operation has not been completed! INFO ID: %d
3115=User canceled the operation.
3116=The volume GUID get failed, didn't copy file to the basic partition. Please copy files to basic partition manually
3117=The individual files can not be copied, please copy files to destination partition manually!
3118=The destination partition lacks sufficient disk spaces.
3119=Open volume failed, you could manually copy files to destination partition. Or restart the computer try again.
3120=The NTFS file system has some errors, can't clone the volume.
3121=Read NTFS file records to fail, there are some bad sectors on the NTFS.
3122=Read sectors to fail, there are some bad sectors on the NTFS.
3123=Initialize the DBR of the FAT failed. Has some errors on the file system.
3124=The conversion is complete unsuccessfully! (Info Code:%d)
3125=Unknown error, the volume can't be converted.
3126=Invalid disk index.
